[ED.
This is the 100-seat parade checking the same line.
I'm leaving from the first floor, but, well, we all wanted to check the second floor first.
Oh, dead dead dead dead.
Oh, no, no, no.
Thank God, I'm leaving from the first floor.
Thank God.
I love you! I love you! I'm gonna run as fast as I can.
I love you! I'll always love you! I'll scream it out as loud as I can
I love you! I love you! You're making it hard to breathe
I can't keep it down, I can't keep it down, I can't keep it down, I can't keep it down
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it before you do
I'm gonna get your feelings right now
Pride get it before you say something
I'll do whatever my heart's synbility and my will dictate
Because I love you
Love Full Game
Roll up your shirt cuffs
I feel the sun approaching
Remember from my heart
I'll always be here because I love you
I've never noticed love in the crowd
Because I love you, just the thought of seeing you
I'm filled with warmth
Eternity ahead
Love must mean happiness
I loved you so much
We're just looking at each other
Even though our lips are so close
Next up is this song. Please listen to this one!
I'd like to say that's why I'm doing this, but
I don't know why I'm telling you now
Two people's home after school is complete
Mukashi barashi
Uh Uh Uh Uh
Who else would be hanging up the phone?
You had me
That's why I'm so happy
Uh Uh Uh Uh
Please stay where you are
Get me high
You in love
This is him.
I'll put on a white T-shirt and change right now
Lure you in, take your heart away
The D melody is up to about the chorus yesterday. I'll go that far, please.
What a good job you did!
The picture left on my face.
Two people in prophetic swimsuits smiling
When love was in full swing
There are things you don't realize
Time flies by in the blink of an eye
Whoever dreams and reality are already gone
My heart and body are swaying
Oh your rumarma
Tell me it's already a lie between you
We'll stare at each other till dawn
I'll believe you
Lumarumarma of love
The halls are out of place, the shoulders are up and down
Even though I know it's there, I can't stop thinking about it
When I fall in love
And yet I'm worried
Thank you for watching
How long do I have to wait to see you?
Shall I say something surprising?
I've been singing full, live, and alone a lot of things.
I only got to sing the second chorus.
Oh, you think it's okay?
I've never sung at a window or on a staircase.
I've never done that before.
Oh my God.
If I hadn't sang solo once.
I would have left by now.
I'm 17. I stand out.
Oh, well.
I thought we were done rehearsing.
I thought we'd just keep going and going.
I was told the night winds were coming through.
Just keep it moving.
We're just going in?
Yurin won't make it.
Yurin won't make it!
And Yuki-chan won't make it either.
Impossible, impossible!
I knew it! It's so noisy!
So many of them!
Oh no!
Everyone's slapping their faces so fast.
It's hilarious. Watch this.
It's amazing!
I really wish I could finish this in another half hour or so.
But we're not done yet.
Today, too.
I'm going to make up with U-PINK!
It's so busy!
I'm looking forward to it!
We made it just in time.
I even managed to put on my cosmetics!
First of all, 7 songs!First, seven songs.
After we do seven songs.
We washed up and changed our clothes, and then the night breeze
I'm flapping my wings, I'm flapping my wings
Singing like that.
It's hard, isn't it?
For us, of course.
But more than anything, I think the concert is for the fans.
For three years, we've been working so hard to keep our voices up.
And for those who put up with the games coming
I want to express my gratitude to those who have continued to support us.
I want to express my gratitude to them.
I would like to express my gratitude to all the fans who have been supporting us for the past three years.
I hope you all will join us and show your support!
AKB48 is going to 2023!
Cutter!
Chasing the running bus, I'm you
I wanted to tell you
In a world where the second person can't see you
I'm trying to turn you away, but you'll find me again soon
Could it be... could it be...
Flying Get! I'm one step ahead of you
I'll get your feelings right now
Flying Get! Before you say something
As long as it feels good
Love you again
I'm in love, don't go back
Now it's you, now you smile, now you run
Your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name is your name
I'll always be here because I love you
I'll always be here because I love you.
I love you
Because I love you
Just the thought of seeing you
Fills me with warmth
You're shining brighter than ever
I'm sure you're happy now
I loved you so much.
We loved each other so much
We used to love each other so much
Our lips are so close
We're so close.
Thank you for your time!
Thank you for watching.
I'm on your end. I want to carry you on my back.
I've been waiting to hear from you.
I know you're busy at work today.
But your asphalt is so lonely underfoot.
I just want to kick you one thank you.
I miss you so much I could cry
I'd like to fly through the night sky right now
And if you were right next to me
I never meant to be you
From the cymbals of the wind
From the thunder
All the way down.
I'm standing right there, facing that place.
♪ The stars are shining down on me ♪
It has to be you.
It's the only star.
A little way to love the earth
I'm the only one who's looked over my life's history
I'm the only one who can set the standard for love
I'm just joking, I'm just joking, I'm just joking
I miss you so much that it sparkles and rings
I want you to visit me right where I am
Somewhere I'll get on and sing a song about the times
I'm not just gonna go back to my room alone
by H. R.
I'll see you
Tonight I'll stay here till dawn
I don't know why I care so much
So that tomorrow I'll see you again
I just don't want to see
ah...
Well missed! It's done! Nervous!
I was so nervous, my heart was racing, I was singing along, my hands were all over the place...
But the fans were so blue, and they re-entered the stage!
I was so nervous, but the fans were so blue, and they made it Team B blue all at once!
I could see a lot of Naruma, and I was so happy to see him.
After I sang my first song, I got a lot of applause!
Wasn't that so great?
It's like, "Oh, my God!
But, you know, when I lay down like this and sang for 2 or 3 seconds...
When you go up like this, "Yo ka, se-no"...
I sang, "Yo, ka, se-no.
That's my only regret.
Dancers came this time just for YOKAZE.The Heart Touch Game
Now, please, something beyond the conscious mind.
It'll be over in a flash. Choco misses of the past.
I'll take it out of the bowl, but I'll put the topping on.
I'll tell you what's good about it, though. It's questionable.
I heard your answer once.
You are my one and only
One and only From the stage
I'm talking to myself.
Talking to myself
That's not why I'm talking.
It's just that it happens.
You don't forget things you don't like, do you, Watagamari?
I'd like to say that's why I'm doing this, but it's too late to do anything about it.
I'd like to say this, but I don't know if I can do it now.
Uh, don't you just want to put your heart and soul into this guy?
Ah.
Uh Uh, don't mind me as I am today
Let me have you tonight
Let's go from there
I'm not afraid of getting hurt
No matter what happens, don't flinch
I'm going to find my dream
No matter what tries to keep me from going
Every time I get hurt, I grow up
Tears in my eyes, I'll put my dream on the line
But I'll never give up on my dream
I'll be the first rabbit
A.B.D.A.B.D.A.B.D.
That's too sad.No, it's not.
That doesn't change the fact that I'm still the same person.
I haven't decorated it since.
I can't forget.
That's how I feel.
I'll always love you.
This is so neat!)
Even if you break up with me, I'm still interested in you.
If I like you, but I don't...
Thank you for watching.
# I know who you are
# I told you it was a lie
But if we stare at each other till dawn
# And I'll believe you
# I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done
# That's enough, that's enough, that's enough
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done
I can trust you
# It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Whose weakness is this?
# I care if you're smiling #
# If I liked you, I'd clap my hands
♪ Hey! What's up!
♪ Hello? Hello?
♪ Dance the same old dance ♪
♪ Hey! What's up!
♪ Hello? Hello?
# Love in my life #
# Right in front of me #
# Tomorrow, forward #
Thank you for watching.
I don't mind you being you.
I bet you can hear me say "seiro.
Like your car, you've gotten used to the dullness.
I want to deliver my spirit of sound to you.
I always love you.
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Instagram & Twitter
I'll never forget this day
See you in 10 years, I'll be waiting for you in this place
Shine brighter than ever
Graduation is not in vain, I whispered a vow
Soon, under the rhythm of love that burns and dissipates
Be my darling
I'll walk out on my own
So that I can protect you more
Hearing your cheers on this stage
I know you're all cheering for me, too
I feel like I'm doing AKB just for this one moment.
I felt that everyone was so warm and supportive of this AKB group.
You are supporting this AKB group.
Like Minazawa-san.
You're so warm and kind and passionate.
I'm so happy to have such warm, kind and passionate people here.
I'm really happy to have such warm, kind, and passionate people here.
Thank you all so much for today.
Oh!
Last one! Ready!
Okay, so there you go.
Now please listen to the last song.
Honest Man.
Ooh!
I hear the staff.
I'm going to speak up! Se-no!
Go on, go on, go on, go on, go on!More and more and more and more and more!
I'm gonna make a sound!
I'm gonna make a sound! I'll scream! I'll scream! I'll scream! I'll scream!
I'll scream!
I like you.
I don't care if you give it to me
I don't want to interfere with your true feelings
I don't want to get in the way of your true feelings.
I love you
No matter what you've been through
I don't want you to swallow
Don't let it swallow you up
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work!
The concert is over!
Look at the result of my hard work!
I lost... three... nails...
I lost 3 fingernails!
It was fun, very fun!
This concert was
I knew it... I knew it...
Riding on the trolley
I was able to get close to the fans by walking in the parade.
and the sun came out... I really enjoyed that kind of flashy
The sun comes out...Of course dancing and performance are important, but
But also
I mean, there's a lot of glitz and glamour
I could feel that we were performing as idols.
It was so much fun!
Another concert...oh yeah!
We have another concert in the summer!
We will have a team concert in August.
I hope you can come and enjoy it again!
So, thank you for your hard work!
I have tomorrow off!
I'm off tomorrow! I'm going to take it easy!
I'm seriously confident I'll sleep until 4am!
Woooo!
Thank God! That was fun!
Thanks for all your hard work! Thank you so much!
See you soon!
Please subscribe to our channel!
undefined